

07 Gbede Street, Bickersteth Estate, lwaya,Lagos. 08126477066 tonyobi98@gmail.com

### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Creative and strategic Marketing and Public Relations specialist offering expertise in social media management, media relations, partaking in Marketing and PR campaigns. I enjoy creative problem solving and getting exposure on multiple projects. I will excel in the collaborative environment of your company. I am a team player who offers creativity and professionalism.

### **PROFESSIONAL SKILLS**

- · Market research
- Brand management
- Promotional campaigns
- Social Media Marketing
- Search Engine Optimisation
- · Search Engine Marketing
- Digital marketing

- · Advertising coordination
- Product Development
- Customer Management
- Microsoft Office Suite
- Social Media Management
- Google Analytics/Adwords
- CRM Tools

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **Marketing Manager**

#### Radeus Business Technology

## April 2022 - February 2023

- Developing and implementing marketing strategies for new products.
- Developed and led team's efforts to increase online presence.
- Planning, directing and executing corporates events.
- In charge of handling and maintaining relations with clients.
- Confer with production, graphic design and web-design personnel to coordinate production of corporate communications materials.
- Developing and implementing public relations strategies.
- Analysing marketing performance using different metrics and tools available.

# **Marketing Manager**

#### Gemnita Hair

### January 2021- February 2022

- Developed marketing strategies and campaigns to promote the brands.
- · Analysed data and metrics to evaluate the effectiveness of marketing campaigns and refine strategies
- accordingly.
- Collaborated with other teams to develop integrated marketing campaigns.
- Conducted market research to identify consumer needs, preferences, and behaviours.
- Implemented strategies that grew total following to 12k followers, which simultaneously increased sales
- volume
- Analysed market trends and consumer behavior to develop marketing campaigns that resonate with the
- target audience.

### Social Media Manager

#### Kunmi Exchange

## May 2020 - January 2021

- Created the content calendar across the social platform to coincide with new marketing strategies.
- Completed competitive research and benchmarking to further understand target audience and goals
- Monitor online presence of company's brand and engage with users, strengthening customer relationship.
- Analysed and reported social media and online marketing campaign result.

# **EDUCATION CERTIFICATION**

## **University of Lagos**

Google Digital marketing Skills Fundamentals of Digital Marketing